careerworkonline.com 2013-12-01

# Career Work Online | Privacy Policy

**General privacy statement**

Career work online administration can used your email address or personal information details to contact you via your email from time to time about issues linked to our website, for example sending you a password reminder or changes in our website that can affect you. Subscription information also provided you time to time if changing or any issue case.

Your email address or any other element of your personal information will never be used for any kind marketing reasons or be revealed to third parties. You will be able to take away any of your personal information stored in our website career work online.

Career work online can  use your IP address to help identify troubles  in case with our server, to administer our web site career work online, and to keep a record of pages accessed by our visitors. Your IP address is used to collect broad demographic information. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.

This information could be shared with advertisers only. This site has links to other sites.  
We are not accountable for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

**Security**

We have applied rational technical measures designed to secure your personal information from  
unintentional loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. But, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

If we ever change this privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page and inform by email all our users so that anyone may be aware of them and they will be given a chance to ask us not to use their information for the changed purposes.
